本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
破烂熊电影专题之史蒂芬.金系列
魔女嘉莉 Carrie
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译&校对：不知深浅
时间轴:knlight
传过去! 传过网!
Set it up! Over!
当前比分 1 5比1 4 这边的队发球
Game point: 1 5-1 4. This team serves.
好 发球!
Service!
快点!
Come on!
往嘉莉那边打! 她肯定接不到
Hit it to Carrie. She'll blow it.
别搞砸了 嘉莉 接住球!
Don't blow it, Carrie. Hit it!
嘉莉! 又是你 你又搞砸了!
Carrie, you blew it again!
- 有她在 哪个队都赢不了 - 瞧她那蠢样儿吧
-Can't win a game with her on the team. -Look at her.
吃屎去吧你!
You eat shit!
救命啊! 帮帮我!
Help me! Help me!
嘉莉 来用棉条啊
Have a tampon, Carrie.
诺玛 看看嘉莉 她来事了
Hey, Norma. Carrie's got her period.
帮帮我啊! 救命啊!
Help me! Help me!
给你擦擦吧
Clean it up.
嘿! 垫上这个吧!
Hey! Plug it up!
怎么了这是? 你们这是在做赛前动员么?
What is going on? ls this a pep rally?
苏 你在干吗?
Sue, what are you doing?
嘉莉 刚刚来事了
Carrie just got her period.
谁来事了? 你在干吗?
Who's got her period? What are you doing?
好了好了 别这样!
Come on. Stop it!
放松 平静下来 听我说
Relax. Calm down. Listen to me.
没事的
lt's okay.
站起来 把自己弄干净
You're going to stand up and take care of yourself.
坚强点 站起来把自己弄干净 快点!
Grow up. Stand up and take care of yourself. Do it!
你看见了么?
Did you see that?
你们给我走 马上给我出去
Get out of here right now.
快走!
Move!
嘉莉 对不起
l'm sorry.
我不知道你的事 对不起
l didn't know. Okay? l'm sorry.
振作点 你不知道这是怎么回事么?
Come on. Don't you know?
听我说 我会解释给你听的
Listen. l'm going to talk to you about it.
冷静 放松
Calm down. Relax.
看见啦? 她们都走了
See? They're all gone.
没事的 会没事的
lt's going to be okay.
怎么会花这么多钱?
How come they're so much money?
我参加自己的高中舞会  还要交这么多钱么?
For my own high school prom, l have to pay that much money?
我能不能多拿一张票?
Could l have two tickets?
她现在才来月经? 年纪够大的啊
lsn't she a bit old for her--?
是初潮
Her first period.
莫蒂 直到半个小时以前我才知道  她以前对这种事情一无所知
Morty, until a half-hour ago, l don't think she knew there was such a thing.
真是难以置信 现在这年代 一个高中女生 竟然不知道这些...
Hard to believe in this day a girl in high school wouldn't know something.
- 常识 - 她就是不知道
-Facts. -She didn't.
我们都知道 她有那样一个母亲 这也就不足为奇了
That shouldn't surprise us, knowing that mother of hers.
- 可我们无权干涉一个人的信仰 - 这我知道
We can't interfere with people's beliefs.
- 那其他那些姑娘... - 嘉莉总是她们欺负的对象
-As for the girls-- -Carrie's always been their scapegoat.
- 你采取些措施吧 - 我会的
-You'll have to do something. -l will.
事实上 莫利 我能理解她们的感觉
The thing is, Morty, l knew how they felt.
这事儿让我对她也有点不耐烦 你知道我的意思吧?
The whole thing made me want to shake her too. You know what l mean?
- 老天 只不过是来月经而已嘛 - 还是让她回家吧
-lt was just a period, for God's sake. -We'll send her home.
芬琪小姐  请让嘉茜・瑞特进来吧
Miss Finch, send in Cassie Wright.
是嘉莉・怀特
lt's Carrie White.
- 请进吧 嘉茜 - 是嘉莉
-Come in, Cassie. -Carrie.
芬琪小姐 请你拿张请假条来好么??
Miss Finch, would you bring in a dismissal slip?
今天剩下的课不用上了...
Take the rest of the day...
你先回家吧... 好好休息一下 嘉茜
...and go home, take care of yourself, Cassie.
发生这种事情我们感到很抱歉
We're all sorry about this incident.
我叫嘉莉
lt's Carrie.
谢谢
Thank you.
需要到医务室去看看么?
Would you like to go to the infirmary?
- 到那里躺一会儿 - 我想嘉莉可以回家的
-Lie down for a while. -Carrie can go home.
想坐车回家么? 我们可以帮你叫辆出租车
Would you like a ride? We could call you a cab.
我相信她走着回去没问题的
l'm sure she can walk home.
这周你就不用来体育馆锻炼了
You're dismissed from gym for a week.
待在自习室就行 好不好?
Take study hall instead, okay?
发生这种事情我们很抱歉 嘉茜
We're sorry about this incident, Cassie.
我叫嘉莉!
lt's Carrie!
讨厌鬼嘉莉! 讨厌鬼嘉莉!
Creepy Carrie! Creepy Carrie!
两年前 你是不是在芝加哥?
Were you in Chjcago two years ago?
- 芝加哥? - 是的 比尔 芝加哥
-Chjcago? -Yes, Bjll, Chjcago.
对 我那时是住在芝加哥
Yes, l was ljvjng jn Chjcago.
你知道这事的 我告诉过你 不是么?
You knew that. l told you that.
不 你没有 是我自己发现的
No, you djdn't. l found out.
- 哦 怀特夫人 - 您好么 史奈尔夫人?
-Mrs. White. -How have you been, Mrs. Snell?
- 挺好的 - 医生先生呢?
-Fine. -And the doctor?
也挺好
Fine.
- 那您女儿呢? - 苏也很好
-And your daughter? -Sue is fine.
- 怀特夫人 请进吧 - 哦 谢谢您
-Won't you come in, Mrs. White? -How kind of you.
- 嘉莉和苏有时在同一班上课吧 - 是啊
-Carrie is in some of Sue's classes. -Yes.
找个时间 可以让她去您家拜访一下
Perhaps sometime she might like to visit.
史奈尔夫人 我奉上帝的旨意来到这里
l'm here on the Lord's work, Mrs. Snell.
来向您宣扬上帝的福音 以基督的圣血之名 我们得到救赎了
Spreading the gospel of God's salvation through Christ's blood.
哦 是的 当然了
Yes, of course.
我要告诉您一些事情  您和医生先生肯定都会感兴趣的
l have something here l know will interest the doctor and you.
通过基督的十字圣架  孩子们也会被引上救赎之路的
The Teenager's Path to Salvatjon Through the Cross of Jesus.
我想苏可能对此不感兴趣吧
l don't think Sue would be interested.
哦 史奈尔夫人 现今的世上  孩子们都在罪恶的荒原上踯躅迷失
The children are wandering through the wilderness of sin these days.
我家的苏是好女姑娘
My Sue is a good girl.
史奈尔夫人 现在的人们匮乏信仰啊
These are godless times.
让我们为此干杯吧
l'll drink to that.
这些书我们会好好读的
We'll all read these.
不好意思 您先请坐
Excuse me. Please sit down.
喂 贝蒂啊 我一会儿打给你好么?
Hello. Betty, can l call you back?
- 玛格丽特・怀特在我这里呢 - 不会吧 你在搪塞我吧
Margaret White is here.
- 是怀特 等我把她打发走了再给你电话 - 等等 你说真的...
White. Let me get rid of her and l'll call you back.
我给您带来一些东西 史奈尔夫人 我想您会受益匪浅的
l have something here that l think you might profit from.
怀特夫人 我愿意给您捐5--
Mrs. White, l'd like to contribute five--
10元钱
Ten dollars.
我明白了
l see.
我为您祈祷 早日找到我主耶稣
l pray you find Jesus.
她不是嘉莉・怀特的妈妈么?
Wasn't that Carrie White's mother?
- 我没听见你回来了 - 她来干吗?
-l didn't hear you come in. -What'd she want?
喂?
Yes?
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道你听着呢
l know you're listening.
下楼来
Come on downstairs.
妈妈?
Mama?
是谁?
Who was that who called?
谁打的电话?
??
你现在是个女人了
You're a woman now.
你为什么不告诉我啊 妈妈?
Why didn't you tell me, Mama?
"上帝用亚当的肋骨造出了夏娃"
''And God made Eve from the rib of Adam.
"夏娃由于软弱 将黑乌鸦带到了世上"
And Eve was weak and loosed the raven on the world.
"乌鸦其名 叫做罪恶"
The raven was called sin.''
- 跟着我说 "乌鸦其名 叫做罪恶" - 你为什么不告诉我 妈妈?
-Say it. ''The raven was called sin.'' -Why didn't you tell me, Mama?
快说! "乌鸦其名 叫做罪恶"
Say it! ''The raven was called sin.''
- 不要 妈妈 - "乌鸦其名 叫做罪恶"
No, Mama. ''The raven was called sin.''
"交合是一等大罪" "交合是一等大罪"
''And first sin was intercourse. First sin was intercourse.''
- 我没罪 妈妈 - 快说!
-l didn't sin. -Say it!
妈妈 我没罪!
l didn't sin, Mama!
"交合是一等大罪"
''The first sin was intercourse.''
''And the first sin was intercourse.''
我当时吓死了 我还以为我要死了
l was so scared. l thought l was dying.
其他的女孩子都嘲笑我 朝我扔东西
And the girls laughed at me and threw things at me.
"夏娃软弱" 快说! "夏娃软弱"
''And Eve was weak.'' Say it! ''Eve was weak.''
- 快说 女人! - 不要 妈妈!
-Say it, woman! -No, Mama!
"夏娃软弱"  "夏娃软弱"
''Eve was weak.''
"上帝降罪于夏娃"
''And the Lord visited Eve with a curse.
"赐她鲜血的惩罚"
And the curse was the curse of blood.''
你应该早告诉我的 妈妈 你应该告诉我的
You should've told me, Mama. You should've told me.
哦 上帝啊! 拯救这个满身罪污的女人吧 让她认识到自己生命的罪恶
Oh, Lord! Help this sinning woman to see the sin of her days and ways.
告诉她 如果她清白无罪...
Show her that if she had remained sinless...
鲜血的惩罚就永不会降临在她身上...
...the curse of blood would never have come on her.
她一定是受了魔鬼的诱惑 有了不洁的想法
She may have been tempted by the Antichrist and had lustful thoughts.
- 我没有 妈妈! - 别对我说谎 嘉莉
-No, Mama! -Don't lie to me, Carrie.
我看透你了 我能看见你的罪恶 上帝同样也能看见
l can see inside you. l can see the sin as surely as God can.
-放开我 妈妈 你弄疼我了 -我们来祈祷吧 祈祷吧 女人
-Let me go. You're hurting me. -We'll pray. We'll pray, woman.
为我们罪孽深重的不洁的灵魂  向我主耶稣祈祷吧!
Pray to Jesus for our lustful, sinful souls!
"上帝降罪于夏娃 赐她鲜血的惩罚"
''God visited Eve with a curse. And the curse was the curse of blood.
然后他降下了第二项惩罚 这就是生育的痛苦
And He visited with a second curse. And this was the curse of childbearing.
以此增加血与痛的惩戒
And He brought forth pain and sweat and blood.''
《创世纪》 第一章 16节
Genesis 3:1 6.
妈妈 让我出去!
Mama, let me out!
让我出去 妈妈  求您了!
Please let me out, Mama. Please!
放我出去! 上帝啊!
Let me out! God!
我们的天父--
Our Father who art in heaven--
谢谢 妈妈
Thank you, Mama.
现在你可以去睡觉了
You can go to bed now.
力量啊 多么神奇的力量
There js power, power Wonderful power
羔羊的鲜血里 蕴含着的力量
ln the blood of the Lamb
嘉莉?
Carrie?
- 把门打开 - 门开着呢 妈妈
-Open the door. -lt's open, Mama.
刚才是什么声音?
What was that noise?
什么声音?
What noise?
上床睡觉去
Go to bed.
好的 妈妈 我正在做祷告
Yes, ma'am. l'm saying my prayers.
"你们会为我们留下些什么呢...
''What are you going to leave for us...
...你们享受着香车惬意...
...you people in your big cars...
...却不断地将大气污染
...spewing pollution into the air?
你们迈开大步 高歌猛进...
You people with heavy feet...
身后留下的 是践踏破碎的旷野家园
...trampling down the wilderness.
你们这些人啊 偷偷溜进我们的车里...
You people who peer into the back seats of our cars...
又从后门旅馆后门鱼贯而出
...hours after you come out of the back doors of your motels.
就这样吧 不久之后 我们所拥有的 就只是彼此而已
Soon, all we will have is each other.
这对我们来说 已是足够...
And that could be enough...
...如果你们肯留给我们  充足的空间 新鲜的大气...
...if you will let us have room enough and air enough...
...和平安定的生活...
...and peace enough...
...我们就能籍此 彼此相亲相爱...
...to love each other...
而这些 你们永远无心给予"
...as you never could.''
我得说 我必须承认...
l must confess...
这首诗显示出了非凡的才华...
...this poem displays the most extraordinary talent.
至少你能写出这个来就够有才华了  汤米・罗斯
Talent extraordinary for you, Tommy Ross.
汤米 写诗和橄榄球比赛得分以及本垒打还是有区别的
This is slightly different from running touchdowns and hitting home runs.
诸位同学 有什么评论么?
Class, any criticisms?
有谁来说说么?
Anyone?
很美
lt's beautiful.
嘉莉・怀特! 你说很美!
Carrie White! Beautiful!
很美
Beautiful.
美啊!
Beautiful!
哦 广袤的天空 美啊
''Oh, beautiful for spacious skies.
琥珀色的麦浪 美啊
For amber waves of grain.''
嘉莉 你说的是指这种美么?
ls that the beautiful you mean, Carrie?
恐怕这不能算是评论吧
l'm afraid this is hardly a criticism.
狗屁
You suck.
汤米 你说什么?
Tommy, did you say something?
- 谁? 我么? - 对 就是你
-Who, me? -Yes, you.
我是说 "够精辟"
l said, ''Aw, shucks.''
- 现在点名 布莱克 - 到
-Roll call. Blake. -Present.
伯恩    格尔根
Born. Gaugin.
格雷斯    哈根森
Grace. Hargenson.
李顿   麦德雷克
Litton. McDermit.
奥什   波莱克
O'Shea. Pollack.
雪瑞斯  史奈尔
Shires. Snell.
沃特森   威尔森
Watson. And the Wilsons.
好 现在排队
Line up.
给我排队! 动作快!
Line up! Move it!
站起来 排成两排
On your feet right now. Two lines.
艾丽丝和玛丽 向前看
Alice and Mary, eyes front.
卡蒂!
Katie!
还有你 克莉丝
You too, Chris.
- 把口香糖吐掉 - 我该吐到哪里呢 柯林斯小姐?
-Spit out that gum. -Where will l put it?
我才不管 你咽下去也行 把它从你嘴里弄出来就行
Choke on it, for all l care. Just get it out of your mouth.
诺玛 把你的傻笑收起来
Wipe that smirk off your face, Norma.
我告诉你们 你们昨天做的事情非常无耻 简直无耻之极
l want you all to know you did a really shitty thing yesterday.
你们当中有没有人想过 嘉莉・怀特也是有血有肉有感情的人?
Did any of you ever stop to think that Carrie White has feelings?
你们有人想过这个么?
Do any of you ever stop to think?
没有 我猜你们满脑子想的都是舞会的舞伴...
No, l guess you're too busy thinking about your dates...
还有参加舞会的事情...
...and the prom.
克莉丝 你有选择了吧
l guess you can take your pick, Chris.
- 你舞会上的小王子是谁呀? - 比利・诺兰
-Who's the lucky guy? -Billy Nolan.
- 谁? - 比利・诺兰
-Who? -Billy Nolan.
- 我听不见 大点声 - 比利・诺兰!
-l can't hear you. Speak up. -Billy Nolan!
那他可是太幸运了哈!
lsn't he the lucky one!
你呢 苏?
What about you, Sue?
- 谁是你的舞伴? - 汤米・罗斯
-Who's taking you? -Tommy Ross.
很好
Right.
对于你们这次小小的恶作剧呢 我的意见是...
Now, my idea for this little trick you pulled...
停课3天 并且扣发你们参加舞会的门票
...was three days' suspension and refusal of your prom tickets.
什么?
What?
老天!
God!
这让你们不知所措了吧 是不是?
That'd get you where you live, wouldn't it?
这是你们应得的惩罚
And you'd deserve it.
因为我想 你们没人认识到...
l don't think any of you have any idea...
自己做的事情是多么过分
...of just how nasty what you did really was.
但是教务处决定  只让你们做一个礼拜的额外锻炼
But the office has decided you're to have one week's detention.
不过 我仍然是教练  额外锻炼内容由我决定和负责
Still there's one little catch. lt's to be my detention.
每天50分钟的时间...
That's 50 minutes every day...
地点在田径运动场... 就从今天开始
...starting today on the athletic field.
- 听明白了吧? - 我才不去
-Get the picture? -l'm not coming.
随便你 克莉丝
That's up to you, Chris.
你们也是 随便你们选择
That's up to all of you.
逃避额外锻炼的惩罚就是...
Punishment for skipping detention...
...停课3天...
...is three days' suspension...
并且取消参加舞会的资格...
...and refusal of your prom tickets.
还有别的想法么?
Any other thoughts?
很好 那现在换衣服去吧
Good. Now change up.
- 你们干吗去? - 不得不去了
-Where are you going? -l can't stay after.
- 快走吧 - 我才不去
-Come on. -l'm not coming.
- 你不想参加舞会了么? - 我就是不去
-You're gonna miss out on the prom? -l'm not coming.
我可不能错过舞会
l'm not gonna miss the prom.
妈的
Fuck.
1  2  3  4
One, two, three, four.
2  2  3  4
Two, two, three, four.
3  2  3  4
Three, two, three, four.
4  2  3  4
Four, two, three, four.
5  2-- 用力做 诺玛! 努力!
Five, two-- Energy, Norma! Come on!
8  2  3  4
Eight, two, three, four.
伸展运动 2  3  4
Stretch, two, three, four.
伸直 诺玛 伸直喽
Stretch, Norma, stretch.
1  2  蹲   起
One, two. Bend. Up.
加快速度
Faster.
抬高膝盖 1  2
Get your knees up. One, two.
加油 青春的姑娘们
Come on, you hotshots.
她真是让人忍无可忍
She can't get away with this.
- 我要找她理论去 - 算了吧 克莉丝
-l'm gonna get her. -Let it go, Chris.
该死的 我这就去!
Like hell l will!
时间还没到
The period's not up.
- 我不管 - 继续做
-lt is for me. -Keep running.
- 还有1 0分钟 - 去你的吧 你这--
-There are 1 0 minutes left. -Stick them up your--
你这么做肯定没好下场 你这婊子!
You'll get canned for this, you bitch!
你再说一句我就揍扁你 听懂了么?
One more word from you and l'm gonna knock you down. Do you understand me?
只要我们团结起来她就没好果子吃! 诺玛?
She can't get away with this if we all stick together! Norma?
海伦?
Helen?
- 苏! - 闭嘴吧 克莉丝 别再废话了
-Sue! -Shut up, Chris. Just shut up.
这事儿没完 我发誓绝对没完!
This isn't over. This isn't over by a long shot!
你不用参加舞会了 哈根森
You're out of the prom, Hargenson.
好了 闹剧结束
The show's over.
继续 跑起来!  1 2 1 2
ln place. Run! One, two. One, two.
"心灵遥感
''Telekinesis.
是指一种超自然能力...
Thought to be the ability...
...它能够通过意念的力量...
...to move or to cause changes...
来操控物体 达到目的"
...in objects by force of the mind.''
- 教练说我可以参加全国联赛了 - 真的呀?
-Coach said l'm in the nationals. -Are you kidding?
太棒了!
Terrific!
怎么了?
What's up?
- 能和你谈谈么? - 现在么?
-Can l talk to you? -Right now?
- 是重要的事情 - 好吧
-lt's real important. -All right.
如果我请你为我做件事  一件很特别的事...
lf l asked you to do something very special for me...
你会答应么?
...would you do it?
你说吧
Yeah.
我想让你带嘉莉・怀特参加舞会
l want you to take Carrie White to the prom.
在镜子里看是什么样的?
How's it look in there?
- 嘿 弗莱迪! - 去敏斯基酒馆混混怎么样?
-Hey, Freddy! -Want to go to Minsky's?
- 哦不了 改天吧 - 你这混蛋!
-Some other time. -You pussy!
- 给我来点啤酒 - 给 别呛死你
-Give me a beer. -Suck on this.
嘿 兄弟!
Hey, man!
- 妈的 - 看着点啊 你这蠢货!
-Shit. -Watch it, you stupid shit!
别那么说我嘛
Don't call me that.
看你干的好事!
Look what you did!
蠢货!
Stupid shit!
- 我说了 别那么说我 - 小心!
-l told you not to call me that. -Look out.
小子 找死吧!
Dumb punk!
- 你刚才害怕了? - 你想害死咱们么?
-Are you scared? -You want to get us killed?
缺心眼
Dumb shit.
去你妈的!
You fuck!
好吧 我答应你
Okay, l'll do it.
别这么着急啊
Don't be in such a hurry.
好了啦
Come on.
"别这么着急" 我恨不得马上离你远点 知道么?
''Don't be in such a hurry.'' l'm hurrying away from you. You know that?
- 不 你才不会呢  - 就像有锥子在扎屁股一样
-No, you're not. -Pain right in the ass.
- 你不是认真的 - 我不是认真的
-You don't mean that. -l don't mean that.
你简直就是个疯婆子
You're crazier than a son of a bitch.
来嘛
Come here.
哦 妈的
Oh, shit.
老天 你是怎么了?
Jesus Christ, what's wrong with you?
能不能等一分钟?
Can't you wait a minute?
为啥? 我们从来都是想到就做的啊
What for? We do this all the time.
你真是屁都不懂
You're so ignorant.
所以你才喜欢我嘛 是不是? 我知道
That's what you like about me, right? l know that.
胡扯
Bullshit.
难道不是? 难道不是?
?
我知道你喜欢我什么 就是这个 是不是?
l know what you like about me. This. Don't you?
该死的蠢货!
Dumb shit!
我告诉过你别那么说我! 你根本就是个贱人
l told you never to call me that! You know, you are totally fucked up.
就是这样 你就是这样 我知道
That's it. You really are. l know that.
我知道的一清二楚
l'm convinced.
比利?
Billy?
过来
Come here.
比利 好啦
Billy, come on.
好啦
Come on.
我想让你帮我做点事
l want you to do something.
啥事?
What?
是很重要的事
Something important.
- 比利 我恨死嘉莉・怀特了 - 谁?
-Billy, l hate Carrie White. -Who?
- 嗨 嘉莉 - 嗨
Hi, Carrie.
- 你怎么样? - 很好
-How are you? -Okay.
那就好
Good.
你干吗呢?
What are you doing?
看书
Reading.
哦? 看什么书呢?
Yeah? What are you reading?
关于缝纫的
lt's about sewing.
缝纫? 不错
Sewing? That's good.
如果你还没有舞会的舞伴的话 你愿意和我一起去么?
lf you don't have a date for the prom, would you like to go with me?
- 什么? - 去参加舞会
-What? -To the prom.
就在下周五 我知道这邀请有点晚  可是我一直有事--
lt's next Friday. l know this is late notice, but they stop--
嘉莉 听我说
Carrie, look.
你们继续 继续练习
You guys, go on. Practice those drills.
我马上就来
l'll be right there.
嘉莉?
Carrie?
嘉莉
Carrie.
怎么了? 发生什么事了?
What's the matter? What happened?
没什么
Nothing.
又是那帮女孩子么?
Was it one of the girls?
她们有人欺负你了?
Did one of the girls do something to you?
没有
No
那是怎么了?
What is it?
你可以相信我的 知道么?
You can trust me. You know that?
告诉我吧?
Would you tell me?
有人邀请我参加舞会
l got invited to the prom.
那真是太好了! 太棒了啊!
That's great! That's fantastic!
那你干吗闷闷不乐的样子?
So why are you moping around?
邀请我的是汤米・罗斯
Tommy Ross asked me.
那更好了
That's even better.
他很可爱呀
He's really cute.
我知道他交往的人是谁
l know who he goes around with.
她们又要戏弄我了 我知道
They're trying to trick me again. l know.
或许不是呢
Maybe not.
我是说 或许他是真心邀请你的
l mean, maybe he really meant it.
我们来想想
Let's think about this.
这可能是件好事呢 你会很开心的
lt might be terrific. You might have a really good time.
嘉莉? 我得和你谈谈
Carrie? l want to talk to you.
谈谈你对自己的态度和看法
lt's about this attitude you have about yourself.
你总是这样 披着头发 挡住脸 闷闷不乐 躲躲藏藏的
You're always walking around with your hair down, moping around.
你这小傻瓜
You big silly.
你来看看自己
l want you to look at yourself.
看看这样如何?
Would you look at that?
看嘛
Come on.
多漂亮的姑娘 看看你的眼睛
That's a pretty girl. Look at your eyes.
涂点睫毛膏就会让它们闪亮动人
A little mascara to bring it out.
嘴唇呢 搽上点儿口红
Your lips. Try some lipstick.
你有很好看的嘴唇 还有颧骨
You have nice pretty lips. And your cheekbones.
还有你的头发 很美的
Look at your hair. lt's beautiful.
可以扎起来 再烫点卷
You could put it up a little. Maybe add a little curl.
你觉得如何?
What do you think?
很不错
Yeah.
说吧?
Well?
- 你想知道什么? - 为什么汤米会邀请她参加舞会?
-What do you want to know? -Why Tommy asked her to the prom.
- 说啊? - 是我让他去的
-Well? -l asked him to.
为什么?
Why?
为什么这么做?
What for?
你心里打的什么主意?
What could you have had in mind?
我是想 这对嘉莉来说是好事...
l thought it would be a good thing for Carrie...
让她参加集体活动 和别人交往
...to get her to join in with a few things and be with people.
- 让她能被大家接受 - 是的
-Make her a part of things. -Right.
算了吧 苏 我们都不傻
Come on, Sue. We're not that stupid.
- 嘉莉也不傻 - 或许是吧 我不知道
-Neither is Carrie. -Maybe not. l don't know.
你是说你不会去参加舞会了?  你就只是呆在家里 缅怀自己的高中舞会?
You're not gonna go? You're gonna stay home and miss your senior prom?
请进
Come in.
- 什么事? - 是点名册 柯林斯小姐
-What is it? -The attendance sheets, Miss Collins.
谢谢 你知道 没有舞伴是不能参加舞会的
Thank you. You know you can't go without a date.
还有别的事么?
ls there anything else?
- 没有了 柯林斯小姐 - 谢谢 诺玛
-No, Miss Collins. -Thank you, Norma.
你的想法呢?
Which brings us to you.
- 我得去训练了 - 那太糟糕了 不是么?
-l have to get to practice. -That's too bad, isn't it?
- 你不介意的话 这是我和苏之间的事 - 我很介意
-lf you don't mind, this is between us. -l do mind.
要不然咱们就去莫顿先生的办公室讨论这事
Unless you'd like to continue this discussion in Mr. Morton's office.
这算是什么大事啊?
What is the big deal?
因为对于嘉莉・怀特来说这是大事 这你也知道的
Because it is a very big deal for Carrie White, and you know it.
她已经拒绝我了
She already said no anyway.
- 再努力一下 她会改变主意的 - 别想当然了
-With some effort, you can change that. -Don't count your chickens.
- 不许再去了 - 好 我不会的
-Just don't try. -Fine, l won't try.
等一下 这不行!
Wait a second. lt's not fine!
你不能强迫别人不许带哪个人参加舞会
You can't order someone not to take someone to the prom.
我必须得确定你们绝对不会再伤害嘉莉・怀特
l can make sure you don't hurt Carrie White anymore.
我们不是要伤害她 柯林斯小姐 我们是想要帮助她
We're not trying to hurt her. We're trying to help her.
怎么帮?
How?
嘿 汤米 嗯...
Tommy...
要是你和嘉莉一起参加舞会的话 你难道不觉得自己看起来很荒谬么?
...don't you think you'll look silly when you walk in the prom with Carrie?
我们不在乎我们看起来是什么样子
We don't care how we look.
对么?
Do we?
什么?
What?
- 嗨 嘉莉 - 嗨
-Hi, Carrie. -Hi.
嗯 这就是你住的地方是吧?
So this is where you live?
你来干吗?
What are you doing here?
你不邀请我进去么?
You going to ask me in?
为什么不呢?
Why not?
我妈妈在休息呢 你要干什么?
Mama's resting. What do you want?
老天 直奔主题 是不是?
God, right to the point, huh?
- 还是舞会的事情咯 - 我都已经和你说过了
-About the prom. -l already told you.
我知道 不过可别说无论如何你都不会改变主意  女孩子们总是这样说
But nothing says you can't change your mind. Girls do it all the time.
- 你干嘛要这样? - 因为我想
-Why are you doing this? -Because l want to.
- 不 你不是这么想的 - 嘉莉 听着 我不会做我不想做的事情
-No, you're not. -l don't do anything l don't want.
- 我不能去! - 不 你能去
-l can't! -Yes, you can.
- 你最好快走吧 - 除非你答应我
-You better go. -Not till you say yes.
- 不 我不能去! - 不 你会的
-No, l can't! -Yes, you can.
我说过了 我不会答应的!
l said, l can't.
不 你会的
Yes, you can.
- 我求你快走好不好? - 除非你答应我
-Will you please go? -Not till you say yes.
你干吗这么执着?
Why is it so important to you?
不知道 或许是因为你喜欢我的诗吧
l don't know. Maybe because you liked my poem.
好吧 我去
Okay, l'll go.
很好 我8点来接你
Good. l'll pick you up at 8:00.
这是干吗? 我们是要叫这些猪起床么?  噜―噜―噜噜
What's the matter? We gonna wake up the piggies? Oink, oink.
开玩笑可不是好玩的 比尔
This is a hell of a risk for a joke, Bill.
- 你不想干了? - 不是 只是个玩笑而已
-You want out? -No. lt's a good joke.
- 你最好是开玩笑 - 是玩笑 好笑吧
-You bet it's a good joke. -lt's a good joke.
- 看看这个 - 啥?
-Look at this. -What?
- 这些猪啊! - 你说啥呢?
-All these pigs! -What are you talking about?
这些画着的猪
These painted pigs.
这都是那个蠢老头和他的傻侄子画的
The stupid old man and his nitwit cousin painted them all over.
我知道 我和那个给他做模特的女孩出去过
l know. l went out with the girl that posed for him.
- 她就是头猪 - 你能闭嘴不?
-She was a real pig. -Will you shut up?
- 把我弄上去吧 - 小声点儿
-Will you let me up here? -Quiet.
你是去杀猪的吧?
You're gonna kill that pig, right?
猪啊! 到这来 小猪乖乖!
Piggy! Here, piggy!
我要把你们的猪头敲碎...
l'm gonna bash your little heads in...
然后你们就不用再担心什么炸弹的问题了
...and you don't have to worry about the bomb no more.
过来 猪崽子们 过来啊 蠢猪
Come here, little piggies. Come here, sucker.
- 这过来一只了 - 你能不能闭着嘴干活儿?
-Here's one right here. -Will you shut up and do it?
我要让它们享受一下
l've gotta give them a chance to burp.
你杵在这儿什么也干不了 把它弄过来 伙计
You can't do it from standing out here. Get her done, man.
我可不行 你来吧
l can't. You.
我就知道会这样 拿着这个站边上去 你这猪头
l knew this would happen. Just hold it there, you pig.
瞧你那熊样
You're just a fuck-up.
- 快动手! - 你给我闭嘴
-Just do it! -You shut up.
好了 过来过来 来吧
All right, move it out. That's it.
来 出来 好的
Come on. Move it out. Yeah.
真是好宝贝 好!
That's my baby. Yeah!
继续继续!
Do it!
嘉莉 苹果派你一口都没吃
Carrie, you haven't touched your apple cake.
妈妈 我吃那个长疹子
lt gives me pimples, Mama.
疹子是上帝给你的惩罚
Pimples are the Lord's way of chastising you.
- 妈妈? - 什么事?
-Mama? -Yeah?
请您理解 我在努力试着改善和别人的关系
Please see that l've got to try to get along with people better.
你想说什么 嘉莉?
What are you going on about, Carrie?
有人邀请我去参加舞会了
l've been invited to the prom.
舞会?
Prom?
是的 高中舞会 你知道 大家都会去的
Yeah, the senior prom. You know, everybody's going.
是老师这么说的吧 是不是?
lt's that teacher that called, wasn't it?
您看我和您不一样 妈妈 我总是很可笑
Please see that l'm not like you. l'm funny.
所有的同学都觉得我很可笑 我不想这样 我想过正常的生活
All the kids think l'm funny. l don't want to be. l want to be normal.
我想趁还能补救的时候 成为一个完整的人
l want to start to try and be a whole person before it's too late.
- 那个男孩的名字叫做汤米・罗斯 是个很可爱的男孩子 - 不行
His name is Tommy Ross and he's a very nice boy.
- 他说晚上带我出去之前 会来拜访您的 - 我说过了 不行
He promised to meet you before and have me in by midnight.
- 我已经答应了 妈妈 我已经答应了! - 不行不行
l've accepted, Mama!
- 去你的忏悔室吧 - 不去!
-Come to your closet. -No!
我就是这么教育你的么?
After all you've been taught?
不是所有的人都是坏人 也不是每做一件事都是罪过
Everyone isn't bad. Everything isn't a sin.
去你的忏悔室祈祷去 祈求赦免
Come to your closet and pray. Ask to be forgiven.
他是个好男孩儿 你会喜欢他的 你肯定会喜欢他的 妈妈
He's a nice boy. You'd really like him, Mama.
男孩子
Boys.
男孩子 是啊 男孩子
The boys. Yes, the boys.
来月经之后就要找男人了 像发情的狗一样
After the blood come the boys like sniffing dogs.
流着口水 痴痴地笑 发狂地寻找异性的气息是哪儿来的
Grinning and slobbering, and trying to find out where that smell comes from.
异性的气息 异性的气息
Where the smell is.
我知道他们在车里干什么事 我都能看见
l know where they take them in their cars. l see it all right.
- 你不许去 - 我已经答应人家了
-You're not going. -l already said l would.
告诉那男孩你不去了 不然我们就立刻搬家!
Tell that boy you're not going or we're gonna move from here!
我们搬走了 你就再也别想看见那男孩
We'll move. You'll never see that boy again.
- 雨吹进屋里了 - 妈妈 听我说啊
-The rain's coming in. -Please talk to me.
我去关窗户
l'm going to close the window.
请坐下来 好好听我说!
Please sit and talk to me!
我要去 妈妈
l'm going, Mama.
我们的生活会有起色的
And things are going to change around here.
女巫
Witch.
那是撒旦的魔力
That's Satan's power.
这和撒旦没关系
lt has nothing to do with Satan.
是我 我的力量
lt's me. Me.
如果我努力集中精神 我就能移动物体
lf l concentrate hard enough, l can move things.
撒旦如此强大
Satan is clever.
妈妈 我不是特例
Mama, l'm not the only one.
别的人也能做到 我读了有关的书
Other people can do it. l read about it.
我可怜的孩子啊
You poor child.
你难道不知道么? 他附在你的身上 可是他让你对此毫无知觉
Don't you know he doesn't let you know he's working through you?
妈妈 我很清醒
Mama, l'd know.
他附在你父亲的身上 并把他带走了
He entered your father and carried him off.
- 妈妈 他是自己逃跑的 - 是魔鬼引诱他的!
-He ran away, Mama. -The devil tempted him!
他和别的女人跑了 妈妈
He ran away with a woman.
所有的人都知道
Everybody knows that.
你必须弃绝这力量  你必须舍弃它并且永不再用它
You must renounce this power. You must give it up and never use it.
我要去舞会 妈妈
l'm going, Mama.
你阻止不了我的
You can't stop me.
我不想再说这件事了
l don't want to talk about it anymore.
把那该死的灯拿住了
Keep that damn light straight.
快点儿
Hurry up.
小心点你这蠢货 你会把血泼一地的
Watch it, you stupid shit. You're getting blood all over the place.
你说谁是蠢货?
Who you calling a stupid shit?
你他妈的连个灯都拿不住
You can't even keep that fucking light straight.
动作快点吧
Just hurry up.
是 女士 我们已经尽全力做了 老大
Yes, ma'am. We's doin' the best we can. We really are, boss.
快点 我想回家了
Hurry up. l want to go home.
你只要一直对我有激情...
Just keep your tits on...
我保证你就能在时机到来的时候拉下绳子
...and l'll let you pull the rope when the time comes.
我会的
l plan to.
我知道
l know.
欧内斯特 听我说  今晚就是舞会之夜了是不是?
Ernest, tonight's prom night, right?
我没想到你会有兴趣参加
l didn't know you were interested in going.
你这是什么意思? 我也是这学校的学生嘛是不是?
What do you mean? l'm a student here, aren't l?
- 这我不清楚 你是么? - 我当然是啦
-l don't know. Are you? -Sure l am.
我可是热情高涨啊 我也想帮忙出力
l've got so much spirit, l want to be on the committee.
晚了 要是一周前我还可以让你来负责场地布置
lt's too late. l could've used you a week ago for decorating.
不 欧内斯特 我没晚 我这时间刚刚好
No, l'm not late, Ernest. l'm right on time.
我愿意负责收集...
l want to collect the ballots...
舞会之王和舞会女王的选举投票
...for the king and queen and voting.
- 你考虑一下如何啊? - 行 好吧
-Think we can arrange that? -Yeah, okay.
那你6点半到这里好么?
Can you be here at 6:30?
不行 我6点半可来不了
No, can't be here at 6:30.
我8点到这里 怎么样?  8点来的话我没问题
l'll be here at 8:00. How's 8:00? 8:00's fine with me.
- 那也行 好吧 - 我们到时候见
-That'll do. Okay. -We'll see you then.
- 再见 弗莱迪 不用太着急 - 我无论如何都会来的
-See you, Freddy. Take it easy. -l'll take it anyway l can get it.
嘿 海伦!
Hey, Helen!
- 干吗呀? - 你听说汤米・罗斯的事了么?
-What? -Did you hear about Tommy Ross?
- 什么? - 你听说汤米・罗斯的事了么?
- 什么事? - 他要带嘉莉・怀特去参加舞会
-What? -He's taking Carrie White to the prom.
- 不是吧! - 是真的
-No! -Yeah.
什么时候的事啊? 他怎么能这样 那苏怎么办?
When djd that happen? He can't do that. Where's Sue?
- 反正他邀请她了 - 她穿什么去啊? 嘉莉・怀特? 穿麻袋片去么?
-He asked her. -What's she gonna wear? A sackcloth?
快点把这些星星挂好
You gotta keep those stars coming faster.
就好了
They're coming.
怎么回事? 我听说汤米・罗斯要带嘉莉参加舞会?
What's this l hear about Tommy taking Carrie to the prom?
不管你听别人是怎么说的 这是真的
Whatever you heard, it's true.
他干吗要这么做? 大家现在都议论纷纷呢
Why is he doing it? Everybody is talking about it.
是我要求他的 因为我觉得我对嘉莉有愧
l asked him to because l thought l owed it to Carrie.
- 这样的话大家会怎么想呢? - 他们会明白的
-Where's that put everybody else? -They've gotta deal with it.
- 你说什么? - 没什么
-What do you mean? -Just something.
- 你不能来参加舞会的 - 哦 我会来的
-You're not going to the prom. -Oh, l'll be here.
你会来? 你是说你会来参加舞会?
You'll be here? You're going to the prom?
行了别说了 我会告诉你的 你也有份的 别着急
Shut up. l'll tell you later. You're gonna be in on it. Don't worry.
我也有份? 什么啊? 快点 告诉我吧 告诉我
l'm gonna be in on it? What? Come on, tell me.
- 等一下再和你说 - 我现在就想知道 克丽丝
-l'll tell you later. -l want to know now.
你就等着瞧吧
Just wait.
给我点提示好不好? 我不会告诉别人的 我发誓
Can't you give me a hint? l won't tell anybody. l promise.
我一个字都不会说的 我发誓 我是你最好的朋友呀
l won't say a word, l promise. l'm your best friend.
- 快告诉我吧 - 好吧
Come on.
- 要参加舞会你就得租一套燕尾服! - 我只有10块钱
-You gotta rent a tuxedo for the prom! -l only got $1 0.
10块钱你就能租一套礼服了! 不然你就不像样子
Ten bucks you can rent a tuxedo! You don't have to look great.
看看 这衣服帅么?
Does this look nice?
看他简直都美若天仙了 你也能 剩下的日子里你都能自信满满帅气十足
He looks beautiful. You can look good. You can make a good impression.
- 要和我约会么? - 我觉得别扭
-Would you go out with me? -Not with ruffles.
你觉得穿礼服别扭? 你开玩笑 是不是?
You don't have to get ruffles. You always gotta make a joke, right?
- 我确实不喜欢 - 有什么可觉得别扭的!
-l don't like ruffles. -You don't have to get ruffles!
看看怎么样 我是不是像条鲨鱼?
Look. Don't l look sharp?
你穿着挺好的 我穿礼服就不好看
lt looks good on you. l don't look right in a tuxedo.
- 你怎么知道? 你穿过礼服么? - 我没长能穿礼服的身材
-Do you know? Ever put on a tuxedo? -l don't have a tuxedo body.
- 我肯定这家店肯定有适合你穿的礼服 - 我穿着不好看
-l know they have tuxedos here for you. -l wouldn't look right.
我知道他穿什么样的礼服合适
l know just the tuxedo for him.
你们看怎么样?
What do you think?
我很喜欢 帅极了
l like it. lt's terrific.
你看 没啥别扭的吧
Look. No ruffles at all.
红色 我应该想到会是红色的
Red. l might have known it would be red.
是粉红色 妈妈
lt's pink, Mama.
看看这是汤米给我的 妈妈 是不是很漂亮?
Look what Tommy gave me. Aren't they beautiful?
我看得见你那肮脏的赘肉
l can see your dirty pillows.
大家都会看见的
Everyone will.
乳房 妈妈 应该叫它们乳房
Breasts, Mama. They're called breasts.
每个女人都有
And every woman has them.
脱掉你的裙子!
Take off that dress!
我们一起烧掉它 然后做祷告祈求赦免
We'll burn it together and pray for forgiveness.
不 妈妈
No, Mama.
- 他不会来的 - 他会来的
-He's not coming. -He is coming.
别说了 我已经够紧张的了
Stop it. l'm nervous enough.
不 他不会来的
No, he's not coming.
他不会来的
He's not gonna come.
那你就走吧!
Go away!
住手 妈妈! 别再伤害自己了!
Stop it, Mama! Stop hurting yourself!
我是对的 他会嘲笑你的 他们都会嘲笑你的!
l'm right. He's gonna laugh at you. They're all gonna laugh at you!
- 他们不会嘲笑我的 - 现在还不晚 留下来 和我在一起
-They're not gonna laugh at me. -lt's not too late. Stay here with me.
我不想和你待在一起
l don't want to stay with you.
我会去开门 然后告诉他你病了 快改变主意吧
l'll answer the door and tell him you're sick, you changed your mind.
坐下来 安静!
Sit down and be quiet!
- 我会告诉他的 说你改变主意了 - 给我坐下!
-l'll tell him you changed your mind. -Sit down!
我走之前 你给我坐在那儿 什么也别说
Sit there and don't say a word until l'm gone.
我会早点回来的
l'll be home early.
我爱你 妈妈
l love you, Mama.
"汝不应留女巫苟活于世"
''Thou shalt not suffer a witch to live.''
汤米?
Tommy?
我们能不能在车里待会儿?
Could we wait here a minute?
- 你在害怕么? - 嗯
Are you scared?
或许这是个错误
Maybe this was a mistake.
哦 不会的 情况不会那么糟的
Oh, no. lt's not gonna be that bad.
他们都是好人 真的
They're a good crowd. Really.
是真的
Really.
别这么紧张嘛
Don't be so nervous.
另外 要是我自己一个人跳舞的话 我看起来可尴尬死了 是不是?
Besides, l'd look awfully stupid dancing by myself, wouldn't l?
走吧
Come on.
罗斯 要是早知道你这么帅的话...
Ross, if l knew you'd look this sharp...
我宁可带你来而不带...她叫什么来着
...l would've taken you instead of what's-her-name.
别理他们 他们要是欺负你的话...
Don't bother about them. lf they self-destruct...
我就和你跳舞的
...l'll dance with you.
你在哪里买的礼服? 我好喜欢!
Where did you buy that dress? l love it!
- 我自己做的 - 自己做的?
-l made it. -Made it?
- 舞会会场布置得不错吧? - 是的
-Don't the decorations look great? -Yeah.
我真紧张死了
l'm so nervous.
没关系的 和我们坐在一起吧
lt's okay. You can sit with us.
几点了?
What time is it?
- 8点整 - 我得走了
-8:00. -Gotta go.
- 你去哪儿? - 出去一下
-Where are you going? -Just out.
- 什么? - 一会儿见
-What? -See you later.
苏!
Sue!
来跳舞好么?
Would you like to dance?
- 我们能不能再坐一会儿? - 哦 当然
-Could we sit here for a minute? -Sure.
你想干吗都行
Anything you want.
嘉莉
Carrie
嗨 柯林斯小姐
Hi, Miss Collins.
- 你真漂亮 - 你也是
-You look so pretty. -You too.
你美丽极了!
You look beautiful!
谢谢 我知道我没那么好看 不过还是谢谢您的夸奖
Thank you. l know l don't, not really. But thank you anyway.
我可以坐这里么?
May l sit down?
- 请坐这里吧 - 谢谢
-Have a chair. -Thank you.
我去和别人说会儿话
l'm gonna talk to some people.
我还记得我的高中舞会
l remember my prom.
我当时的舞伴是篮球队队长
l had a date with the captain of the basketball team.
他足有6英尺7英寸高
He was 6 feet 7 inches tall.
所以我买了双3英寸的高跟鞋...
So l bought a pair of three-inch spike heels...
这样 晚上我们亲吻的时候 情况就不会...太尴尬
...so our kiss good night would be less awkward.
然后 我们坐进了他的敞篷车里...
So anyway, we went in his pickup truck...
然后 车抛锚了 我们就不得不下车...
...which, of course, broke down and we had to get out...
然后走完剩下的半英里路程去参加舞会
...and walk the last half-mile to the prom.
可是 当我们走到的时候 我满脚都是水泡了...
By the time l got there, my feet were so covered with blisters...
所以我就只能干坐着
...that all l could do was sit.
因为我没法跳舞了 所以我们所做的只是仅仅坐着 聊天
l couldn't dance. So we just sat there and just talked.
不过 那感觉真是神奇
And it was magic.
你的感觉是不是也是这样?
ls it like that for you?
嗯 很不错
lt's nice.
只是很不错?
Just nice?
就像是--
lt's like--
- 就像是飞上了火星一样 - 你会永生不忘的
-lt's like being on Mars. -You'll never forget it.
我相信我会的
l don't think l will.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们在说什么呢?
What's going on here?
- 你在和我的公主说什么? - 聊天而已
-What are you doing with my date? -We were just talking.
一定要开心 好吗?
Have a lovely time, okay?
你也是!
And you too!
再见
Bye.
别让我发现 你也像那样抱别的男生
Don't let me catch you hugging any guys like that.
- 不会的 - 最好是
-You won't. -l'd better not.
绝对不会的
You won't.
你真的一定要这么早回家么?
You really have to be home so early?
是的 我答应妈妈了
Yeah. l promised.
- 很抱歉 - 没关系
-l'm sorry. -That's all right.
舞会过后 有人说要去来温斯顿酒吧
Some of the kids are going to go over to Lewiston's after the prom.
没事
That's okay.
什么?
What?
要是你想和朋友们出去 我不会打扰你们的
lf you want to go with your friends, l don't want to spoil anything.
让我把话说完好不好?
Would you let me finish?
我要说的是...
l was going to say...
如果你愿意的话 我们去蜂巢区待一会儿好不好?
...that if you'd like to, we could stop in at the Beehive.
我从来没去过那儿
l've never been there.
太好了! 那我们一会儿就走
Good! Then let's go.
好么? 说定了哦 很好
Okay? For sure. Great.
做好准备跳舞了么?
Are you ready to dance?
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
来吧
Come on.
我不知道怎么跳 我不会跳
l don't know how. l can't.
你能跳的
Sure you can.
- 我不会 - 不 你能行的 来
-l can't. -Yeah, you can. Come on.
- 把手给我 放在这儿 - 这样?
-Give me your hand. Put it there. -Like that?
放在我肩膀上
Put this on my shoulder.
对 就这样
That's right.
放松 好么?
Just relax. All right?
很好 听着音乐就好 很好
Okay. Just listen to the music. That's right.
看到了? 你能跳的 很不错
See? You got it. That's good.
你跳的不比别人差嘛
You're as good as anyone else out here.
你能行的
You got it.
- 对不起 - 没关系
-l'm sorry. -That's all right.
没关系 一点都不疼 根本没感觉
That's all right. No harm, no foul.
- 我什么都做不好 - 不 你能行
-l can't do anything. -Yeah, you can.
我不会跳舞 我甚至不会--
l can't dance. l can't even--
- 汤米? - 嗯
-Tommy? -Yeah.
为什么?
Why?
什么为什么?
Why what?
为什么我在这里?
Why am l here?
因为是高中舞会啊
Because it's the prom.
为什么我会和你一起来?
Why am l here with you?
因为我邀请你的啊
Because l asked you.
- 为什么你要邀请我? - 因为我想啊
-Why'd you ask me? -Because l wanted to.
你为什么想?
Why'd you want to?
因为你喜欢我的诗啊
Because you liked my poem.
只不过不是我写的 是别人写的
Only l didn't write it. Somebody else did.
嘉莉 我们来参加舞会
Carrie, we're here.
我们两个在一起 我很开心
And we're together and l like it.
真的 我很开心!
l do. l like it!
好啦 女士们先生们 女士们先生们
All right, ladies and gentlemen. Ladies and gentlemen.
你们两个给我注意点儿
You two behave yourselves.
请坐下好不好
Just take your seats, please.
我们现在开始投票选出我们的舞会之王和舞会女王
We've got to vote for the king and the queen.
- 汤米 我们在名单上 - 我知道
-We're on here. -l know.
- 你想放弃么? - 你想不想?
-You want to decline? -Do you?
当然不想!
Hell, no!
如果你赢得了头衔 他们会请你登台 并且为你唱校歌
lf you win, all they do is put you up there for a school song and a dance.
然后 会有人给你拍照 把你的相片放进学校的年鉴...
Then some guy takes your picture for the yearbook...
然后所有的人都能看见我们俩的傻样子了
...so everyone can see we look like a couple of idiots.
这是最后一学年了 干吗不参加呢?
Anyway, it's the last year. Why not?
真是太美了
They're so beautiful.
你是最美的
You're beautiful.
我们要选谁呢? 你的死党比我多
Who should we vote for? They're more your crowd than mine.
我一个朋友也没有
l don't have a crowd.
我们选自己吧
Let's vote for ourselves.
为什么不行?
Why not?
求你了 别选我们自己了
Please don't vote for ourselves.
来吧 就让我们做一次不顾信义的恶魔吧!
Come on. To the devil with false modesty!
那就做恶魔
The devil.
闭嘴 把那个拉紧点儿行不行?
Shut up. Will you close that?
老天! 你想要我们被抓住么?
Jesus! You want to get caught?
那个嘉莉・怀特也挺可爱的嘛
That Carrie White sure is cute.
我记得你说过他们会赢的?
l thought you said they would win?
他们会赢的 然后节目还完不了呢
They will. lt won't even be close.
我已经安排好了
l called in a few favors.
我可以收走你们的选票么?
Can l have your ballot, please?
谢谢 鲍比
Thanks, Bobby.
爱丽丝 我收一下你的选票好么?
Can l have your ballot, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
请交选票 谢谢
Ballots, please? Thank you.
- 弗莱迪 快点 给你选票 - 我来了
-Freddy, hurry up, please. Ballots. -l'm coming, dear.
很好很好 谢谢
Good, good. Thanks a lot.
- 都收上来了么? - 是的
-Did you get all of them? -Yeah.
我扔在你身后了 使劲儿踢
They're right in back of you. Just start kicking.
祝你好运
Good luck.
还有选票么? 谢谢
More ballots? Thank you.
我又给你们送来了一些选票
l have some more ballots for you guys.
女士们 先生们 获胜者已经产生了
Ladies and gentlemen, l've got the winners.
太好了!
All right!
获胜者是汤米・罗斯和嘉莉・怀特!
l give you Tommy Ross and Carrie White!
这怎么回事?!
What the hell?!
他们都会嘲笑你的!
They're all gonna laugh at you!
垫上这个! 垫上这个!
Plug jt up! Plug jt up!
我们很抱歉 嘉茜
We're all sorry, Cassje.
相信我 嘉莉 你可以相信我的
Trust me, Carrje. You can trust me.
来  我们走
Come on, let's go.
- 他们都会嘲笑你的 - 对不起 嘉茜
-They're all gonna laugh at you. -Sorry, Cassje.
相信我 嘉莉 相信我
Trust me, Carrje. You can trust me.
开开门! 怎么回事?
Open this door! What is going on?
救命! 救命啊!
Help! Help!
让学生们都冷静下来!
Get these students to calm down!
弗洛姆先生!
Mr. Fromm!
妈妈?
Mama?
太糟糕了妈妈 他们真的都笑话我
lt was bad, Mama. They laughed at me.
妈妈 抱着我
Mama, hold me.
抱着我 妈妈 求你抱着我
Hold me, Mama. Please hold me.
我和拉尔夫第一次做爱的时候  我就该去死...
l should've killed myself when he put it in me...
结婚前他保证 不再做这种事情了
...after the first time, before we were married.
拉尔夫保证过 他不再做了
Ralph promised never again.
他保证过的
He promised.
我相信了他的话
And l believed him.
但是罪恶无法消逝
But sin never dies.
罪恶无法消逝
Sin never dies.
开始的时候相安无事 我们都清白地生活着
At first it was all right. We lived sinlessly.
我们睡在同一张床上  可是我们不做爱
We slept in the same bed, but we never did it.
然后 那个晚上...
And then that night...
我看见 他用那样的眼神看着我
...l saw him looking down at me that way.
我们跪下来 祈祷神给我们力量
We got down on our knees to pray for strength.
我闻见他的呼吸里有威士忌的味道
l smelled the whiskey on his breath.
然后他抱住了我
Then he took me.
他抱住了我!
He took me!
都是因为那肮脏罪恶的廉价威士忌
With the stink of the filthy roadhouse whiskey on his breath.
可是我却喜欢那样
And l liked it.
我却喜欢!
l liked it!
喜欢他用他的脏手抚摸我的身体!
With all that dirty touching of his hands all over me!
你一出生 我就该把你献给上帝
l should've given you to God when you were born.
可是我太软弱 我退缩了
But l was weak and backsliding.
现在恶魔闯进家里了
Now the devil has come home.
- 我们来祈祷吧 - 好
-We'll pray. -Yes.
我们来祈祷
We'll pray.
我们来祈祷...
For the last time...
来做最后的祷告
...we'll pray.
我们的天父...
Our Father Who art in heaven...
愿你的名受显扬
...hallowed be Thy name.
愿你的国来临 愿你的旨意奉行在人间--
Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done--
贝蒂 是你啊 感谢上帝
Betty, thank God it's you.
要是再来记者我可应付不了了
l don't think l could've handled one more reporter.
是的 我们都要崩溃了
Yeah, well, we're all a little edgy.
她好多了
She's better.
就是睡得太多了 我觉得...
Sleeping too much, l guess...
不过史尼德医生说 在她经历了这些之后 这种情况也在意料之中
...but Dr. Snyder said that's to be expected after all she's been through.
他说她年龄还小 过阵子她会忘记的
He said she's young enough, so she'll forget all about it in time.
不 不 我不会让她去参加葬礼的
No, no. l wouldn't let her go to the funerals.
汤米和其他人都离去了  我们最好也离开一段时间
Wjth Tommy and all the others gone, jt's best we go away for a whjle.
出售 (嘉莉・怀特永远受地狱之火的燃烧!)
没事的!
lt's all right!
没事啊!
没事没事 我在这儿呢
lt's all right. l'm here.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入